elements = [
{
    "question": "How much do you trust this person? (1) very little (5) a lot",
    "answers": {"1": "f", "2": "b", "3": "t", "4": "d", "5": "s"}
},
{
    "question": "Do you keep each other in the loop?",
    "answers": {"yes": "b", "no": "c"}
},
{
    "question": "How much history do you guys have? (1) very little (5) a lot",
    "answers": {"1": "c", "2": "f", "3" : "t", "4": "d", "5": "s"}
},
{
    "question": "Would you go to this person for advice?",
    "answers": {"yes": "b", "no": "c"}
},
{
    "question": "Do you guys talk about a future together?",
    "answers": {"yes": "s", "no": "t"}
},
{
    "question": "Are you attracted to this person mentally or physically?",
    "answers": {"mentally": "f", "physically": "c", "both": "d"}
},
{
    "question": "How long can you guys go without communicating?",
    "answers": {"hours": "t", "a day": "b", "days": "f", "a week": "c"}
},
{
    "question": "Are you guys exclusive?",
    "answers": {"yes": "d", "no": "c", "i don't know": "t"}
},
{
    "question": "Would this person be first to hear your good news?",
    "answers": {"yes": "b", "no": "c"}
},
{
    "question": "Would this person be first to hear your bad news?",
    "answers": {"yes": "s", "no": "t"}
},
{
    "question": "How often do you guys talk? (1) not a lot (5) five+ times a day",
    "answers": {"1": "c", "2": "f", "3": "d", "4": "s", "5": "t"}
},
{
    "question": "Does their family know who you are?",
    "answers": {"definitely": "s", "most of them": "d","some of them": "f", "no": "c"}
},
{
    "question": "Do you guys share things? (snacks, clothes, toothbrush, charger)",
    "answers": {"most things": "s", "some things": "d", "a few things": "f", "nothing": "t"}
},
{
    "question": "Do you guys have common interests?",
    "answers": {"too many to count": "b", "a lot": "t", "a couple": "f", "not really": "c"}
},
{
    "question": "Is the connection between you guys deep or superficial?",
    "answers": {"deep": "s", "both": "t", "superficial": "c"}
},
{
    "question": "How often do you spend time with this person? (1) not often at all (5) most days",
    "answers": {"1": "c", "2": "t", "3": "f", "4": "d", "5": "s"}
},
{
    "question": "Do you have a platonic or romantic feeling toward this person?",
    "answers": {"plutonic": "f", "romantic": "d", "both": "t"}
},
{
    "question": "How hard do you try to maintain this relationship? (1)i don't really try (5) i give it everything",
    "answers": {"1": "c", "2": "t", "3": "b", "4":"d", "5": "s"}
},
{
    "question": "Doe this person take compliments, but not return them?",
    "answers": {"yes": "c", "no": "t"}
},
{
    "question": "How often do you call/facetime this person?",
    "answers": {"mutliple times a day": "s", "every day":"d", "often": "d", "not a lot": "f", "never": "c"}
},
{
    "question": "Does this person say 'I love you'?",
    "answers": {"in light-hearted situations": "f", "when i say it first": "t", "pretty often": "d", "all the time": "s"}
},
{
    "question": "Have you and this person shared low moments together?",
    "answers": {"plenty": "s", "some": "d", "a couple": "b", "none": "t"}
},
{
    "question": "Would spending Valentine's Day with this person be weird or normal?",
    "answers": {"weird": "f", "normal": "d", "a little bit of both": "t"}
},
{
    "question": "Do you have prolonged eye contact with this person?",
    "answers": {"not intentionally": "d", "yes": "c", "no": "f"}
},
{
    "question": "Do you get nervous around this person?",
    "answers": {"yes": "c", "kind of": "t", "not really": "d", "i'm used to it": "s"}
},
{
    "question": "Do you improve your physical appearance around this person?",
    "answers": {"most of the time": "c", "sometimes": "t", "not really": "d", "don't need to": "s"}
},
{
    "question": "How well do you know this person's friends?",
    "answers": {"we've developed a friendship": "s", "farely well": "d", "we're all pretty close": "f", "not well at all": "c"}
},
]
